Contact

palorca.santos@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/palorcasantos-717bbb7b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare
Pharmacy Technicians

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Full Professional)

Palorca Santos

BSN, RN, CNOR

New York, New York

Summary

Experienced Staff Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Health Insurance, Clinical Research, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, and Life Support. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BSc) focused in Nursing Science from CUNY School of Professional Studies.

Experience

Jacobi Medical Center Staff Registered Nurse- Operating Room November 2016 - Present (3 years 7 months) Greater New York City Area

Operating Room Staff Nurse

URBAN HEALTH PLAN, INC. Staff Registered Nurse April 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 1 month) Bronx, New York

Avicenna Ambulatory Surgery Center Staff Registered Nurse April 2016 - December 2016 (9 months) Bronx, New York

Education

CUNY School of Professional Studies
Bachelor of Science (BSc), Nursing Science · (2016 - 2018)

CUNY Bronx Community College
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2012 - 2014)